<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CarouselViewPager</string>

    <string name="americano">A long black is usually served in a taller glass or mug, this is based on a 30ml shot of espresso. Hot water is then added to this and served black. The term \'long\' here refers to the fact that the volume has been increased by adding hot water. For larger drinks a double shot of espresso may be used to maintain the ratio of water to coffee.</string>
    <string name="cappucino">Cappucino can be recognised often by the quantity of foam served on top of the drink. When the milk is being stretched (steamed) the barista will incorporate a greater amount of air into the milk, this in turn creates a greater quantity of foam.</string>
    <string name="latte">A latte is also a milk based drink, how these are served can vary depending on the interpretation of the coffee house you are at. The general rule of thumb with these is that they will be served with espresso, steamed milk and around 1cm of milk froth will settle on top. A skilled barista that can generate micro foam when stretching the milk will often present your drink with some artistic latte art on top.</string>
    <string name="mocha">A delicious combination of rich chocolate flavour and bold coffee that provides a sweet, indulgent treat! The best Mocha\'s will use a dark drinking chocolate mixed with perfectly brewed espresso, gently stirred to combine then served with Latte style steamed milk. The use of a dark chocolate powder ensures that the drink  will not be overly sweet compared to a milk chocolate or syrup. Best enjoyed on a cool winters day, it\'s the perfect mix between a coffee and a hot chocolate. For extra indulgence serve topped with whipped cream.</string>
    <string name="ristretto">A ristretto is a similar style drink to a short black, the difference however is that rather than allowing water to pass through the coffee grounds until you have 30mls of espresso (a single espresso), the extraction would be stopped when you have half that amount - 15mls (single ristretto). The purpose behind this is that by stopping after 15mls, what has been extracted from the coffee grounds is the best tasting components of coffee. After the first 15mls have been extracted anything after this will start to add more acidity, caffeine and generally negative flavours to the drink.</string>
    <string name="short_coffee">A short black is a 30ml shot of espresso served in a demitasse cup, and a good/fresh short black will have a thick golden crema on top. This is of course the basis for almost all espresso coffees.</string>
    <string name="vienna">A vienna is simply a long black served with whipped cream as a replacement for milk and sugar.</string>
</resources>